

Beaula Ekka

Full Stack Developer | UX/UI Designer | Graphic Designer

Profile

Details

I am thrilled to embark on a new journey as a full stack developer. Drawing from my 10 years of experience as a corporate trainer, graphic designer, and IT support provider, I have honed my skills in communication, creativity, and problem-solving.

Address: Zuid Holland Netherlands By transitioning to a junior front-end developer role, I aim to leverage my previous experiences and combine them with my newfound technical skills in Full Stack development and UX/UI Design to create intuitive and visually appealing web applications.

Skills

Employment History

Frontend Stack

Graphic Designer

HTML CSS Freelance, Rotterdam Area, Sep 2013 - Nov 2018

JavaScript

Trainer, Learning and Development

TypeScript React/ Next Automatic Data Processing, Pune, Dec 2008 – Mar 2011 Consultant Trainer Infosys, Mysore, April

eact/ Next 2008 –

2008 - Sept 2008

Vue/ Nuxt Tailwind

Sr. Executive Quality Coach/ HP Technical Support

IBM, Pune/Delhi, Jan 2005 – April 2008

Chakra GSAP

Java

Education

Backend Stack

React Native, Codecademy Feb 2024

Node.js PHP/Laravel Python3

JAVA, Codecademy Jan 2024 PHP, Codecademy Dec 2023 Python 3, Codecademy, Dec 2023

SQL, Datacamp, Nov 2023

Design Stack

Frontend Software Development

Photoshop Illustrator InDesign Winc Academy, Amsterdam, May 2023

Lightroom

UX/UI Design with Figma

Lightroom XD Winc Academy, Amsterdam, May 2023

Figma

Web Development Winc Academy, Amsterdam, Dec 2022

Languages

Google IT Support Professional Certification Coursera, Mar 2023

English Dutch

Delft University of Technology, Talen en Academische Vaardigheden, Aug 2012

Multimedia and Graphic Design Arena Multimedia, Pune, India, 2011

Technical Training, IBM, India, 2005

Bachelor's Degree in Business Administration, 2004

Southern Adventist University, Tennessee, USA off campus site: Spicer Adventist University, Pune, India

Links

Email:Beaula.favejee@outlook.comPortfolio:https://beaula.vercel.app/GitHub:https://github.com/BeaulaEkkaBehance:https://www.behance.net/beaula

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/beaula-ekka-favejee-97316558/